{"sid": "12UIHXSR0Y8F_main", "calc_equals_delay": 5, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 370942, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 370943, "question": "7+3+7+68", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 385511]], "time_left_end": "286", "answered_time": 385511, "user_answer": "85", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "286", "question_time_start": 385511, "question": "23+37", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 388711]], "time_left_end": "283", "answered_time": 388711, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "283", "question_time_start": 388711, "question": "4+3+8+98", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["submit", 394150]], "time_left_end": "277", "answered_time": 394150, "user_answer": "113", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "277", "question_time_start": 394150, "question": "76+47", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["submit", 409766]], "time_left_end": "262", "answered_time": 409766, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "262", "question_time_start": 409766, "question": "3+79+88", "correct_answer": 170, "events": [["calc_3", 421727], ["calc_+", 422994], ["calc_7", 423727], ["calc_9", 424831], ["calc_+", 425360], ["calc_8", 425977], ["calc_8", 426119], ["calc_=", 426903], ["submit", 435655]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "236", "answered_time": 435655, "user_answer": "170", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "236", "question_time_start": 435655, "question": "9+3+13", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 441359]], "time_left_end": "230", "answered_time": 441359, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "230", "question_time_start": 441360, "question": "3+44+28", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 449126]], "time_left_end": "222", "answered_time": 449126, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "222", "question_time_start": 449126, "question": "3+7+4+24", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["submit", 459582]], "time_left_end": "212", "answered_time": 459582, "user_answer": "38", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "212", "question_time_start": 459582, "question": "16+786", "correct_answer": 802, "events": [["submit", 465718]], "time_left_end": "206", "answered_time": 465718, "user_answer": "802", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "206", "question_time_start": 465718, "question": "3+4+98", "correct_answer": 105, "events": [["submit", 469438]], "time_left_end": "202", "answered_time": 469438, "user_answer": "105", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 469438, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "202", "question_time_start": 469438, "question": "3+3+4+49", "correct_answer": 59, "events": [["submit", 476294]], "time_left_end": "195", "answered_time": 476294, "user_answer": "59", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "195", "question_time_start": 476294, "question": "3+73+57", "correct_answer": 133, "events": [["submit", 484350]], "time_left_end": "187", "answered_time": 484350, "user_answer": "133", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "187", "question_time_start": 484350, "question": "99+99", "correct_answer": 198, "events": [["submit", 487814]], "time_left_end": "184", "answered_time": 487814, "user_answer": "198", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "184", "question_time_start": 487814, "question": "73+176", "correct_answer": 249, "events": [["submit", 515430]], "time_left_end": "156", "answered_time": 515430, "user_answer": "249", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "156", "question_time_start": 515430, "question": "8+73+34", "correct_answer": 115, "events": [["submit", 526070]], "time_left_end": "145", "answered_time": 526070, "user_answer": "115", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "145", "question_time_start": 526071, "question": "58+84", "correct_answer": 142, "events": [["submit", 540542]], "time_left_end": "131", "answered_time": 540542, "user_answer": "142", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "131", "question_time_start": 540542, "question": "8+3+9+56", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 546558]], "time_left_end": "125", "answered_time": 546558, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "125", "question_time_start": 546558, "question": "8+8+8+79", "correct_answer": 103, "events": [["submit", 551942]], "time_left_end": "119", "answered_time": 551942, "user_answer": "103", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "119", "question_time_start": 551942, "question": "9+9+93", "correct_answer": 111, "events": [["submit", 559702]], "time_left_end": "112", "answered_time": 559702, "user_answer": "111", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "112", "question_time_start": 559702, "question": "9+9+67", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 570622]], "time_left_end": "101", "answered_time": 570622, "user_answer": "85", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 570622, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "101", "question_time_start": 570622, "question": "3+3+54", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 574854]], "time_left_end": "97", "answered_time": 574854, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "97", "question_time_start": 574854, "question": "7+77+57", "correct_answer": 141, "events": [["submit", 594838]], "time_left_end": "77", "answered_time": 594838, "user_answer": "141", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "77", "question_time_start": 594839, "question": "33+38", "correct_answer": 71, "events": [["submit", 600062]], "time_left_end": "71", "answered_time": 600062, "user_answer": "71", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "71", "question_time_start": 600062, "question": "3+9+3+77", "correct_answer": 92, "events": [["submit", 606030]], "time_left_end": "65", "answered_time": 606030, "user_answer": "92", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "65", "question_time_start": 606030, "question": "6+3+3+97", "correct_answer": 109, "events": [["submit", 615134]], "time_left_end": "56", "answered_time": 615134, "user_answer": "109", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "56", "question_time_start": 615134, "question": "3+77+13", "correct_answer": 93, "events": [["submit", 618878]], "time_left_end": "53", "answered_time": 618878, "user_answer": "93", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "53", "question_time_start": 618878, "question": "37+699", "correct_answer": 736, "events": [["submit", 625102]], "time_left_end": "46", "answered_time": 625102, "user_answer": "736", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "46", "question_time_start": 625102, "question": "47+24", "correct_answer": 71, "events": [["submit", 628958]], "time_left_end": "42", "answered_time": 628958, "user_answer": "71", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "42", "question_time_start": 628958, "question": "8+6+6+23", "correct_answer": 43, "events": [["submit", 634054]], "time_left_end": "37", "answered_time": 634054, "user_answer": "43", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "37", "question_time_start": 634054, "question": "7+7+47", "correct_answer": 61, "events": [["submit", 642350]], "time_left_end": "29", "answered_time": 642350, "user_answer": "61", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 642350, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "29", "question_time_start": 642350, "question": "7+33+53", "correct_answer": 93, "events": [["submit", 650494]], "time_left_end": "21", "answered_time": 650494, "user_answer": "93", "user_correct": "True", "score": "31"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "21", "question_time_start": 650494, "question": "6+8+6+89", "correct_answer": 109, "events": [["submit", 659093]], "time_left_end": "12", "answered_time": 659093, "user_answer": "109", "user_correct": "True", "score": "32"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "12", "question_time_start": 659095, "question": "6+4+34", "correct_answer": 44, "events": [["submit", 663606]], "time_left_end": "8", "answered_time": 663606, "user_answer": "44", "user_correct": "True", "score": "33"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "8", "question_time_start": 663606, "question": "3+7+3+16", "correct_answer": 29, "events": [["submit", 669790]], "time_left_end": "2", "answered_time": 669790, "user_answer": "29", "user_correct": "True", "score": "34"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "2", "question_time_start": 669790, "question": "8+13+46", "correct_answer": 67, "events": []}}}}}